<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Vanilla Outposts Expanded Expanded: Ranch (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.VanillaOutpostsExpandedExpandedRanch</packageId>
  <author>Clown Cat</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/VanillaOutpostsExpandedExpandedRanch</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
    <li>vanillaexpanded.outposts</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Clown Cats mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2797007124

Animals to be ranched must have the trade-tag AnimalFarm, except for Boomalopes. 

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/VanillaOutpostsExpandedExpandedRanch][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[h1]Ranch Outpost:[/h1]
[i]Places a temporary, autonomously-led camp that specializes in raising and butchering animals. Once an ample amount of meat, leather and animal products are collected, a delivery will be made at the outskirts of a faction's primary colony.[/i]

This outpost lets you raise animals and collect animal products such as [strike]Chemfuel[/strike]Milk and Eggs as well as meat and leather from culling older ones. 

To create this outpost you're going to need to create a caravan with a male and a female of the animal you wish to raise along with at least one pawn who's good in animals. The animals will then be raised and reproduce there over time lending you their animal products if any. Once enough animals have been raised it will reach a threshold where your pawns will begin culling older animals(this is based on their animals skills) bringing meat, leather and any butchery results that are produced such as elephant tusks or thrumbo horns. Most of the multipliers can be tweaked in the config and there is an option to let you raise animals that don't graze which is off by default.

This mod is meant to be used alongside Vanilla Outposts Expanded but its not required to function.

[h1]Notice:[/h1]
If you had been using this mod before it was update you have 2 options, either destroy the site using dev mode or use the older version which can be found here https://github.com/spessbro/VOEE_Ranch/releases/tag/old_ranch 
If you decide to choose the latter please do not report any bugs as it is not and wont be maintained in the future.
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2900645347][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/VanillaOutpostsExpandedExpandedRanch?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>